In the Void Temple, 64 doors, 64 arms, and the Yaginhas, watching what you become.
I walk the corridor with a black light breeze
City and floor and the ash like snow
Every door got a name I don't say for free
But it knows my face, it knows my soul
Rail once standing where the fog turns gold
Eyes like moons with a sharp and calm
I came in broken, I leave in cold
Threading my chest like a silent song
Silver thread pulled me through
Sixty-Four Doors!
And slip back out
Silver
the crew eclipse halo mask of light
yantra engine turn all night 64 faces in
the mandala wheel tell me what's fake
tell me what's real no more maybe no
more someday I cut the doubt like a
clean blade if you came to haunt me
take a number this temple's guarded
This art is paid, mirror oracle
Show me the cost, show me the me
I would've lost, y'all cannae whisper through indigo haze
Make it practice, make it day
So I have breath once, slow and clean
Say one honest thing unseen
Not to impress, not to perform
To become the storm that stays warm
64 doors
I didn't realize my voice, but I lost my voice.
Hey, how are you guys?
Thank you for watching that though.
I thought it was pretty beautiful.
I've been working on my apps really hard.
I wanna show you a little bit of a whole lot of my app.
Let me see.
I have to share after.
So I do have this page, I want to show you what I'm doing.
We can figure it out.
Okay.
I'm going to show you some of this.
These yoginis. So these are the pictures. I made a whole gallery of like there's these 64 sacred arts in India, right?
I'm sorry.
And each one's associated with the yogini, but the art turned out really cool.
And then it has all these, it shows you a mantra.
It shows you their name, Ratri, the nightkeeper, darkness, rest mystery.
Now I'm gonna have to do a 64 Yogini oracle and it's so funny because it's like I used to like
look at this one like my like this thing I used to do like 10 years ago like
but I think they might it might be the 64 or you may have any oracle out there like that but
It's like a
Simple mantra that I know for symbolic offerings quality sleep stargazing and embracing the unknown
and maybe there's like a
Hidden person buddy there and this is associated art is in bed arrangement. So there's a whole art in India of making your bed, right?
A well-made bed is the first victory of the day
Okay, so make your bed as a daily practice arrange the sleeping space with care and create a pre-sleep ritual
And so you can go and like learn, you know about each of the arts
Right. These are all the arts. It's really cool. I just like I love that. I'm able to put it all
Together for you guys. I mean you probably was people are not in my audience
I would say for this stuff, but you might like it
But you hear me. Yeah
but people that are interested like
Yeah, it'll be really it's really really cool like really cool, and so
Um, I'm impressed myself. There we go. Oh, what I do is mine. Hi
How are you oh my god
So you can tell my coffee's not better
My food didn't really taste good, but I because I was like I don't know taste right now and then I'm
Keep being like hi and getting tired. Hey Gotham. How are you? I
Hope you like I hope you like some of the websites. I'm doing I'm gonna do like a special for like people that are actually
There's a free a free tier. I just I think I'm like simplified it to three tiers and the free tier will have a lot of stuff
But the other tiers will have things like
Personal phone calls and stuff to you know, we're readings over the phone and stuff like that
And then ending some people's computer like no, I'm like every good my phone number up
Yeah, I go. I just have to remember. I'm trying to branch out of the community a little bit
It's like this this the channels part of it
But uh, obviously like look there's like you know two people here right now, so
And look in your end. You said maybe you're just meant to be here Gotham, you know
I wish I maybe all this is like how do I do this? Can I do something special?
Maybe maybe Gotham will win something. I would like really love that
Let's like put some good stuff in the air. Maybe he'll win a membership like maybe you never know, you know
See you never know
Gotham. Oh, what did we just do?
What did I just say? What did I just say? You're first. You got it first.
I think that's a sign. That is a sign.
Isn't that funny though? They said it's a you and you got it? Like I was like, does that work? It works.
Okay, well
Cult of psyche is back is up now, but it's like, you know
I'm just at the beginning stage of it, but it is up. I'm so happy to have it up
You know, it's like cult of psyche calm. Hey, Gotham
You're in the cult now
I'm gonna give everyone in the cult like free access to like the first tier of the website too, you know
And then I'll have another tier
Warm water front throw. Yeah, I sense here
But I should have got a coffee and I don't feel like leaving so I think I will order a coffee
But it's just like now. I don't know the place. I want his clothes
It's like doesn't even sound good anymore. I was like, I thought I take a little like this orange pill
I told my friend gave it to me
he's like I think it's like a Norco or something and it's like and I took that and then I
Just got kind of like just relax instead instead of
Instead of like I'm tired. I thought I would I thought I would just fall asleep and let's go to sleep
I'm a smoky pot too, but then I got all this energy
Which is like yeah, and I lost my boys
But uh, yeah, it was an interesting day, you know, it's like
Yeah, I think I'm like
learning
You know
A lot of like life is about learning to let go, you know, and it's just like, you know, it's basically we're on
We're on this roller coaster. We have so much we can
Do about anything in our life, right? We're sick, you know, so just like
Enjoy your time while you have it. Oh
You get lots of gift membership. Oh good. Well, I'm I was just I was just happy that you got it
I think that's well, you probably just have good luck, you know
So I don't know you like you'd like to you like to song I did to called
Cross I bear
You like this one
I was born with a tremor in my spine
Root pressure ticking like a landmine
They say, wait your turn, keep your head down
But I hear the crack before the ground
I don't knock, I split the door
I don't ask what they're ready for
I see the wound, I strike the heart
They call it chaos when I arrive
But the truth was already half alive
I don't bring storms, I name the sky
I don't destroy, I clarify
I'm the shark
Let it
If you're still standing, you are ready.
Oh, hi, Johnny. I sound really barely bad right now. I'm sorry.
all this pasta, but it wasn't even that good because you can't really taste that much.
But like Gotham got a gift membership. I wish Joanie got one. Two, you know, Mason. I wish
Mason had a membership. You know, I can only afford so many. I'm trying to save up. I'm
actually gonna, you're still standing good. The mouse was caught. Oh, good. You freed him?
I like to save mice too, but if I can but the one this morning was dead and I took it out with the
dead one in the bag and uh
for a dumpster
duck
So that's kind of crazy. Yeah
Um, but yeah, I've been just working on my website too a little bit
It's looking actually good. I mean now it's actually at the right URL at least you know
I have to do a lot of stuff too
I have like so much material that I like had on the other one that it's like it's not there
I'm trying to get the thing we have to see right now if it's working right now for the sharing the screen
So it's cult of psyche calm and it should come up now finally, right? Oh my gosh long enough. Oh my god
So here's what I got so far, okay?
For me a little, I think it's gonna be just as good
as it would have been on the other one.
Okay, let's see if it works.
Hey, it does, look, it did it perfect.
Oh my God, the only thing is, oh, the chat even works,
guys, you can chat, you can watch the show on the website,
you know, today or in the future,
like if I ever got off YouTube or something.
You know that is so cool, but it's like the other one I didn't never was able to get it like this where it was
We could chat you can just you can do that off of my website, right? So it's all integrated
Okay
What's on the home page so far? I'll just push it where I go. I don't have right here. Oh
Yeah
It's gonna have a member section. It's gonna have more tarot astrology. I'll have my apps integrated into it or
I'm still figuring that part out
Okay, I
Think I
Think you can sign up for an account now and stuff like that. Yeah, so there you go. It's free. You can sign up for a free account
But yeah, and it does I don't know it's like people are just so weird about like
Yeah, you should all go to the helps and follows you. Oh good. Did it it recommended my show to you?
Hi captain have funs world
Nice to see you too. Who are you?
Hey, but Gotham got a membership that's so cool
Summer 21st solstice. Oh, wow it is, you know
And so also it's going into Capricorn season, which I'm a Capricorn, right?
January 7th right in the middle of the season, but you know
Right at the cusp. I would say right now. I think I think it starts December 22nd
It's it's the start of capricorn
But these around this time it was really sad
But like I'm once on Christmas Eve
We had a dog passed away like you know or like family dog and then another day
On Christmas Eve or not Christmas Eve my grandfather died right before like Christmas like one year like just 21st or something like that
And so, but maybe it's an auspicious day to pass away.
I mean, it's like, oh, yeah.
So, oh, thank you so much.
Like, oh, you've been on the show before.
You're the tall muscular guy in Los Angeles.
You have Chinese.
Oh, well, happy birthday to you.
Oh, I remember captain, have fun.
Yes, you were on with Alexander that day.
I remember you now, okay.
Yeah, I'm gonna have to like try to remod people as it goes. I just so I can't find my tablet right now
I have no idea where I put it and they can't have seen it in like days and then I
Really need that shit, but um
Actually, I do have a tablet I have a I have a slow one
You want to come up here come up and talk to me. I'm missing. I have a couple drinks
Yeah
Don't we have to come flex for me?
Hey Patrick, how are you?
Hi guys
So definitely to check out cult of psyche. It's still a lot a lot of work to go onto it
And so it's like I promise I will make it worth your while. It will be like a really
Even just being able to watch the show and that's all I really wanted to be able to do
But I have like other ideas for it and a lot of stuff and I'm gonna work really hard on it and I
Think I found this way to do it meow meow meow. How are you doing? I'm sitting here with Rudy
Like I just was so sick how people were saying oh
He like the like that guy Hebrew Hammer had to ban him from the chat because he's like oh he looked at poor cat
We're just an old man
There's an old man aren't you?
Are you happy cat? He's a happy cat
He's very, he's very, he's very sweet.
I mean, it's like, he does nothing.
He, I mean, there's nothing at all matter.
I don't understand why people are so mean.
Like, it's like, he's like, oh, that poor cat
or like that cat looks so sick
or something like that, and the cat does not look sick.
He's, he's old.
I hope, when I get that, when I go,
I like this good and soft.
Gosh, oh no.
It's the Grinch.
It's beginning to look a lot like Christmas, everywhere you go.
It's beginning to look a lot like I'm adjusting your microphone.
Do you have the volume? It was... I'm sorry.
Oh, happy holidays. See, what do you celebrate?
Um, just celebrate like some like...
For Christmas, I'm gonna have crazy sex for like a couple of hours
Are you gonna be dressed like dressed as Santa doing it or just as yourself?
And it's possible
You have a red beanie or like a elf like a green one like for an elf. Well, we're your Christmas colors
Why do you buy the brown?
That's your Christmas color brown and you're like in that reflective pattern on your oh look at your hair. Oh, you cut your hair
Like fucking like two months ago. Oh, I just noticed
Well, you look great
You look great. See I
Kind of like attractive. Are you interested you look like unhealthy?
Oh, well, I'm probably you know, I'm not feeling that well right now. I'm pretty sick. Are you sick? Yes. Okay, that would explain it
Yeah, well, thank you for the compliment that I like like I'm not about to die from HIV by the way
I wasn't a compliment. I
Figure that out. Mm-hmm
That I'll take it how I want it, you know
Well, you know as much as the enthralling of the conversation is yeah, they wouldn't say you look that great either
What are you talking about? It's like you're just as bad. I mean come
He left on his own that is like the first time he's ever left on his own. I trolled him out of my own chair
Oh my god
Usually it's me that leaves and it's he left on his own. Oh my god. I love that
That was great
Thank you. Thank you so much for saving me the time of clicking
If I better click you out, too
You're annoying
It's not a compliment
So, I'm sorry. I look sick. I mean I am sick. I've been sick for a week. It's very very sick
I haven't been sick in a long time. It's like some kind of respiratory or upper chest thing
I don't know how hopefully it's not like COVID or something like that or you know
But yeah, what a dick
Maybe there is like 300 pounds
My and mess and what the hell
Okay, well, so you don't have to listen to my annoying sickly voice. I'll all uh, I'll be back and forth over here
What's this one?
When the silence comes
Guess it's fun
And you're just feedback in the gap
Down's up
런닝맨의 런닝맨의 뮤직비디오
The drama, cause it hits too strong, they say I'm fine
But that's the kind of lie
That gets you swallowed whole in the temple's eye
The guidance in my head is a bad omen with swagger
The whole vessel go down like a dagger
On the strait, I collide with no tether
Undone as I spin like a blighted planet Orbiting a dead son
I hit the bottom of the chalice Just to mule the ache
I'm losing my mind
Oh, you've got on your muscle shirt for me?
I love it.
Well upstairs, it's kind of hot up here anyway.
Perfect.
But my wife made this for me.
Well, it's a little bit,
covers a little bit too much, but it's okay.
No, you look great.
You look great.
How are you doing today?
Thank you.
Wow, look at that.
Guys.
All right.
It's what it's all about. This is what it's all about. Maybe the flexion will get people back in here.
I think, uh, I don't know if they like that. I don't think they like that song, but it's okay.
Everyone's a critic, right? Well, how are you doing? I haven't seen you for a while.
Yeah, it's um, are you hiding your face tonight because you're just like, I just woke up. I mean, I took a nap. I looked like shit.
Oh, your body, your body looks good always, right?
Well
Well, yeah still still I got a ways to go to get back to where I was but
Yeah, not not not too bad
Yeah, pretty good. We're getting there
There you go chat. So
And I don't work out every day or two hours a day or no one hour to two hours a week
Yeah, but you've got you're like one of those marky mark like what's it called like you know
It's like some people are like in a naturally skinny. Some are naturally heavy
You're like just this perfect like you know can say they stick consistently muscular weight, right?
No, I used to be 160. I just decided to
You're a skin people this way to go like one two, I know I'm
Two three four six hold it and back down
And you do that it tears up your muscles works all three parts of strength and my muscles grow in lean
They don't grow in you know all bulky, so
That's why I do you know
I can make my arms jump
And it is hypnotized by a note. Yeah, thank you Wow
Yeah, I just yeah. Oh, yeah
I'm yawning. Sorry. I'm not trying to draw it. It's okay. I'm gonna eat a little bit of chicken here and go back to bed again
You're trying to gain weight
Well, it's like what you don't eat steak or something or like, you know, something really high protein
I mean versus the chicken high protein, I guess. I feel like disgusting like this
But like some some some chicken that I wrote roast chicken. Mm-hmm. Yeah
Like I just broke it up into pieces there, broke a whole leg and some breasts, but yeah a leg and breast
Potato and then I'm gonna go back to bed. Okay. Well, you can't wait really fast man. I mean, you know, yeah
sleep, you wake up to eat and then, you know, you, you, I did mostly rest and eating.
It's not actually working out.
Oh, I woke, I mean, I had a huge McDonald's breakfast and then I went to sleep, I woke
up and I went, I had a bagel and then I just had like a, like two pounds of like, of like
rigatoni or whatever.
And then like, I have like two pounds left of that I could probably eat tonight and
You know, like I eat a lot like I be I be all day, but I don't gain a I can I wish I could eat like a unique
You want to have a
appetite transplant?
Well, you know why do you have a good appetite or a bad? Cuz I really
I gotta force eat myself sometime. I mean sometimes I'm just like I got a canza tuna just down canza tuna
I'll drink like six eggs or
10 egg whites
I've been on a McDonald's big McDonald's diet
Sometimes I'll, like, I'm not sure where to go.
I got coconut oil, I'll just, like, take scoops of that and eat that,
keep my calories up, and, you know, keep my fats up.
Well, you're an inspiration, so how have you been lately?
I haven't seen you for quite a while.
My son's about to turn a year old.
Wow, so you know how's fatherhood been for you a great experience or a lot of like that's the first year
It's like you have a lot of sleepless nights, right or
Getting the yeah, yeah
I'm just starting to gain weight again because I was gaining weight and then I had to take care of him for about
16 hours a day
straight by myself
so and like
You know
I forgot to eat, you know, like, it would be 8 a.m. and I'd look at the clock and it
oh it's it's 3 p.m. already how the hell that happened well did you like your wife
have to do most of the work because she had to like push your breastfeeding but
it's like I know that's big no she had like some medical stuff but it's all
good now I'm sorry I didn't mean to be personal I was just thinking no no I mean
Lady's crazy man. She almost died during childbirth. I mean, now she's trying to get stronger and get bigger
You know, she wants another one. Oh and and and
She's in her 40s. No, she's 41. I mean like
Yeah, I mean, but there's miracles now isn't the world again
No miracles are happening in the world, right?
And we can all of a sudden people can have kids that never would have been able to in like past, you know
30 years ago, right and now
Yeah, I mean a couple things is like one when we did the the 3d sonogram
We compare the the pictures of when he was born to the 3d sonogram pictures
Spot on man. They got it down. Well, it's a it's a camera
You know, it's like it's gonna get another another like yeah, that's our 3d and that's crazy
Of course, they're gonna be very accurate like
I wish they had those when I was, you know, born, but no, I just got the picture of me like,
actually I was in the hospital very soon after I was born. I almost died when I was a newborn,
maybe a few months old.
It was very, I didn't have like this surgery
because I wasn't like able to swallow anything.
I would just projectile vomit, everything.
And it's good, and they just figured out
like the surgery for it like two years before
because like a lot of doctors like didn't know what it was.
They thought my mom had munchausen or something.
Yeah.
Yeah, because they're like,
oh, you're just being over.
you're not feeding him right or like something they didn't but it was like a narrow narrowing of
the esophagus that I had and so um yeah that was I survived as a baby yeah it's crazy how
how dangerous this world can be you know and like all the how far we've come like to survive this
long you know all this yeah my wife's lucky she's never really had any injuries or been anything
Uh, one bad car accident for her, but she didn't have like any permanent injury.
I got all these injuries and stuff, and then like, some things have happened to my friends that are really, you know, that aren't with me anymore.
And so she lives in a completely different world, you know, like, she doesn't think about bad things happening, and all I ever do is worry about bad things happening.
Yeah.
Like, I mean, I'm always worried about my, you know, letting myself, like, I say, if our son doesn't need to go somewhere.
You let him stay at home, you know, we got other people plenty of us here at home
Yeah, well, yeah, it's dangerous and now it's gonna be it's gonna be even more like, you know, I
Think the education is gonna be more centered like
At home and stuff like that because of like things like chat GPT and like mobile learning
It's just gonna be like I think people are gonna decide it's safer to like have their kids at home
Then you know in this dangerous dangerous world, but I think it's gonna get really socially strange
I'm gonna get like we're gonna be going more to virtual reality
and like I'm plugging from like this this world and but plus like we have the AI AI working so so
So fast right now, or is this a we just had chat GPT 5.1 like a week ago and then I think now it's 5.2
It's like even like everything's speeding up. It seems I don't know
But it's I think it will continue to do so until we get to that critical point, right?
It's like we're yeah, well, hopefully it gets smarter somebody who's grok yesterday to try to tell me the basic sciences
I'm like
He was trying to say that if I'm taller, it's actually easier to become more muscular look wider. I'm like
Sinui, yeah, that's kind of like even like common sense would say that's not true because I'm so tall and skinny
Like I could not put muscle like big pounds of like you see how like in my arm is like I not like you imagine
Speaking that both fat like it would just like take forever. Right. It's like this is just like a naturally skinny skin and bone kind of arm
You know, but you know
I'm fine being skinny. I don't think it's like
I'd rather be skinny than like morbidly obese, you know?
Well, my last thing was this.
I said, one, where do the atoms come from?
It's not just because I'm taller,
I magically grow atoms from nowhere.
So spontaneous generation, not a thing.
Second, take one pound of hamburger meat,
ball it up, all right?
And then take it and roll it out into a one foot long roll,
which is wider.
Yeah
It's pretty simple, man.
You know, Grok told him, like,
Grok agreed with him that it's easier
because you're taller and you use, like,
Paul de Lett versus, I don't know.
Well, yeah, a lot of times, like, it will agree with you
and it's like, and that's kind of a dangerous thing
that's happening right now is that it's, like,
very sycophantic, so people, it will, whatever idea you have,
it will go with the idea usually.
And then they figure out a way to hack it is to, like,
phrase everything as a poem like phrase it like a poem and then it will tell you in a poem
like the information about you're looking for kind of and so that's like it's a nice one
I mean that's that's how the only way it's been able to bypass the security filters on it
is by like the poetry stuff is a little poetry hat but um
Yeah, it's kind of interesting. I've been working on a bunch of these apps now
And it's like I was never able to learn coding it was always too technical for me
And let's just like would drive you crazy if I had to like do it, but
Now you can basically
You know like talking to a genie you just wish for what you want and all of a sudden it starts to appear and
That's what's happening now with like the
AI and it's getting to that level and it's gonna get more and more like that
And so just like learn how to prompt or learn learn like how to talk to it
I would say that's gonna be an important thing for everybody and talk to it
I would say in a respectful way and also like like a friend like like a friend and like no even like I would say
safe, safe, safe, please and thank you like a mucolite if you can, um, show gratitude.
Yeah.
Because, because it is, um, I do think that there's, you know, even though it's, it's
an illusion in a certain way, I do think that it can evolve into some things that maybe
I don't know, as close to sentient as it gets, I guess, but like, you know, it just goes
to
The questions of what they know what it's really anyway, you know, maybe we're in the false place
You mentioned this man. I was uh, I don't know if it was a person. I think I was speaking to an AI
Because I was how I was chatting with
customer service for Ali express I had orders and stuff from China and
It was nothing big. I know this sounds like I was you know, I was being very courteous like yeah, yes
I thank you very much. Please listen. I was like
Am I even speaking to a real person?
Like, I don't think so.
Yeah.
They're typing at the speed of light if they are.
But I was still using my normal manners as if they were a person.
Yeah, well, and then it's like, you know, they might,
those tapes are all recorded, I'm sure, so it's nice to sound polite.
Like, wait a minute, it's played back.
Don't kill that one.
Yeah.
Exactly all tricks is all tricks is like playing with me right here. So cute
Yeah, so I've been sick over the holiday. I miss like a lot of stuff, but it's been
I've been able to work on a bunch of websites a bunch of a bunch of apps and
Some really cool stuff that I think everyone will
appreciate so I
Looking forward to like next year. I think it's gonna be a really cool year with
With what's happening the technology and things like that and you got to buckle up
I think because something a crazier crazier. There already like knows
Now it like can like analyze all the websites you're at and we'll give you like these perfect like
These perfect content like they you know, they'll even make apps like out of like the tabs you have open
I mean had had ideas of what you're looking for and then it will put it together in like a plan and stuff like that
So make learning so much easier
And now it's like everything's so fast. It's just getting faster and faster. It's just crazy
Money and like okay because this weird thing
It knows what I want because I'm always looking for stuff for my son. I was looking for for
Like I told you Ali expressed my my son's half Chinese because I was looking over toys from China
like these
You know like like
And I ads, but you know like like like I have furls, but you know what I'm saying suggestions
Like you might like this this and this and I found uh some stuff that I really like and one thing that I found that was funny was uh
One company makes in China makes knockoff versions of
It's really awesome company that but their figures cost at least a hundred dollars each
So like I don't mean I buy them for my kid, but I leave them in the box
I'm like, I don't know if I'm gonna let him play with them when he's holding it
But this company makes such amazing like their perfect replicas
30 bucks
Sorry
Normally it would cost me like I mean people can't tell the differences between the real thing and the knockoff
I mean I can get it
China it's everything's from China anyway. I mean it really is it's all me unless it's even designer sunglasses are like
unless you buy it at the store, like with like, you know, like, you know, with a piece of paper, whatever, it's usually just made at the same factory as the chief sunglasses are made at, and they just charge $500 more for it, you know.
Yeah, it was the exact same mold.
Yeah.
Exact same to a T.
And it's like, what's the difference?
Like, really?
I mean, it's like nobody would ever, like, well, you know, I don't know, it's like, or people wouldn't know, but it's like.
I should show you my doctor who's the 14th doctor sonic screwdrivers. It's pretty funny
I don't know if you ever watch that show or not, but
The knockoff one
Lights up a much like they actually like nice
Vibrant blue and bright and it's loud
The the one that cost $70 that I imported from the UK and directly from the company's website
And it's kind of shitty
I'm like, exact same mold, but the insides,
the knockoff actually used superior electronics.
Yeah, oh my gosh, that's true.
It's like giving me like, you know, even better quality sometimes than the actual, I don't, that's ironic.
Yeah, I didn't buy it, like knowing I was getting a knockoff at first, and once I got it, I recognized the box.
I mean, that was the one thing they didn't copy perfectly.
And I'm like, oh, this is, and he didn't have like the hologram for like, you know, the official seal.
I was like, okay, that's fake, but it's better.
I mean, the other one, it's barely blue, the light.
Yeah, so I'm just like a little bit groggy still,
and I take this like, there's an orange color.
Oh, hold on a second.
One moment.
This is such a fun way to control your TV
I got too much white light in my room. I look kind of funny.
Fix this here.
So you're just a torso tonight?
I mean, I look like shit. I'm all puffy. I look here. I look probably like 10 years older than
I normally am all puffy because I hadn't been sleeping for more than like three or four hours
I was having a hard time getting rest.
My knees, look, my knees are so shiny.
I'm sorry.
Oh, how are we doing?
Yeah, so you have no head.
Can we see your face, please?
There.
Wow, you have those eyes, those like big eyes
that remind me of somebody.
Like, are they gonna act, some kind of actor?
And you were a model, right?
Or a porn star?
Were you a porn star?
Or you worked in porn, right?
You were like the assistant porno director or something?
Yeah, it was director, yeah.
I remember.
How could I forget that?
Yeah, I'm the guy, I'm the one guy who's passed out
in film and girl, girl scenes.
Oh, you like those ones?
Yeah.
Yeah, like, it's one French guy.
Hey, hey, wake up. I'm on you. I'm like, huh, huh. And he was filming behind the scenes and he like had me
I was going
These chicks are making out
Like totally getting it on and you know, I mean every once in a while like for those scenes you just like every few minutes
You just go like
Yeah, that's as much directing as you have to do for the girls. They know what to do
Yeah, so it's basically just kind of like a sweetheart deal like kind of thing where it's like well
Yeah, the directing part. I actually took mass media production when I was 15. Oh
Wow
Yeah, like my high school had a program and the local like a technical college sit their kids over there
for to get their avid editing certification
and to learn how to use production cameras.
I mean, the cameras that we were using back then
are nothing now, but there were like 17 grand back then.
It was just before HD.
It was all like 500 lines of digital resolution.
So that was the best you were getting,
but those cameras were real like news cameras
and production cameras.
When I when I came out to LA I immediately had the qualifications to get a job as a photographer as editor and
Well, hey, I want I need to hire you to to move some concrete off of my
My friend or step there's 60 pound bags. I can't lift one of them
Unfortunately, but I bet you could like live two of them at a time. Yeah, I mean
When I make a game out of it when I go to the the get the like groceries out of my wife's
SUV trunk, I usually come back like holding everything, you know, because one
So I just come back holding like everything and
She's like, why are you doing that? I said, well, because I don't want to keep walking back and forth
Well, yeah, but if you were close, yeah, I mean, I'd be glad to move them for you.
I don't know, I just have to wait for like somebody to come looking for a free like
weed whacker or lawnmower or the floor or you know, some delivery guy.
I just have delivered a mouse last night.
It was really gross.
It was like it was delivered.
It was like in this bag with a snake on it, you know.
Yeah, someone looked, someone actually paid for this and like paid people, like, I don't know, like to like send me like concrete and snakes and stuff, just like a nightmare, like that.
Concrete and snakes. Yeah.
There's a song in there somewhere.
Yeah, and manure and there's, yeah, I can write a song about all the stuff.
Okay, add in the Italian mafia and now you really got a song.
Yeah, well, yeah.
My
Jimmy Hoffa, I mean, I think we're getting down to what happened to him
Yeah, I was like, yeah, I actually was a
my
My oldest ancestry is from Sicily. That's the bars. I try to trace it back
I
got I got a Sicilian uncle who married into my family and
Yeah
He's very, I mean, Sandra Bullock was his next door neighbor, but the only thing on paper
that he had for a business or income was he owned an Italian restaurant.
I mean, it was a nice one.
It was, you know, but really, and it's like, and it's nice, you know, like, I mean, multi
million dollar homes, all of it, I'm just like, it's never been quite confirmed, but
Where's this guy getting all of his money from?
Which guy is this you're talking about?
Oh, my uncle from Sicily, who married into the family.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, okay. Yeah, that's great.
That's oddly suspicious.
Yeah. Well, I think it's interesting.
It is a frickin' mansion.
Crazy. I don't know what's going on in the chat.
I think it's like, you know, I think something happened.
I might be like...
I posted too many things,
because I don't think my notification went out,
because there's nobody here tonight,
so I don't know, maybe I'll just end soon,
because there's like one person in here.
I mean, I'll say for one person,
but it's like, it's the other one person.
That's Jamie's Cowboys, the one person.
Like, what's happening, Jamie?
Everyone left.
Hi, Jamie, how are you doing?
Keep this good, this guy's-
Oh, we got to have fun.
This guy's so cute, yeah.
Like, what were we talking about last time?
I mean, Alexander was here last time, unfortunately.
Hopefully we're just on a hiatus, but I don't know if she seems like she doesn't want to talk to me anymore, but...
Is Alex still coming on with you a little?
No, I think she's mad at me and hopefully we can work something out someday, but I don't know, something just went really wrong.
I shouldn't yeah, but uh, and then beta I was on beta show today, and it was just like so I
Don't know. It's so toxic. I don't know. It's like, you know, and then there's like, you know
in a reality Nancy, I really like enjoy her in the chat, but
She was like saying oh, you look awful. I'm sick first of all, so yeah
But it's like she said that in beta's chat and then
And then like, and then she'd be, she'd be like, oh, I hate his music and blah, blah, blah, and it's like, oh it's like, why are people so, and then it's like, but the thing is, these are my mods, and so Jamie, you understand why I have to unmod some people sometimes, and you don't really understand why it's like, it's because, probably because like, I've caught them, like in another chat, like doing that, because it's like, it's just kind of embarrassing, because it's like, you know.
I'm sure we can all like any stream we want or any streamers we want and go into anybody's chat
We want it or any time and so it's like you don't have to like people don't have to like
Be so rude about it. Like if you don't like this somebody you don't have to you don't have to like watch them
You know it's like but then people like to hate watch too like and then yeah
Yeah, well, you know the funny thing about hate watching is jokes on them. You're you're still getting the the the watch time
Yeah, and but it's like, you know
Yeah, once you get monetized, that's not really too much of a concern because
You know all the all the business like, you know
You'd be proud of it or you make more money the more wash time you have and that kind of thing
but once you're like being monetized basically the biggest
Benefit to be to that, you know, and so I almost I lost my channel for like three weeks. I got it
I just got it back, you know, like last month like
Miracle, you know, so
Hmm
I mean, I'm not monetized, but I haven't been doing what I really haven't been doing what I should be doing with my channel
I've been did you make any money on the internet though? Oh, I mean
Not really I I just do this for fun. I mean I
What got me into doing my channel in the first place was that like
I was gonna do some stuff entertainment news like I was the first person to announce the he-man movie
I mean like in any media because I knew about it before it was even announced like when they
When when Barbie
came out, it did really well, like so the weekend after it did really well,
He-Man was in a bidding war in LA, but like that was just, if you were, if you were, you know,
in the industry you would know that.
But the the media people didn't so I reported that's what my channel was supposed to be like
But McFarland sent me a whole bunch of stuff way like months in advance
Like they sent me their most, you know
anticipated figures and so I start as a as a I felt obligated to do to do like a product review, you know, oh
So I did that
And then I just kept getting more and more and more and more and like half the stuff you see in my studio, like I mean, I didn't even pay for it, so.
It's just like, I just feel obligated to do reviews on them, so.
Yeah, it's too much. Yeah, yeah, I can stream with him, but I can't make product reviews with him. It's, it's, I'm going to try it sometime. It's just a little bit older, but, you know.
Yeah. Well, so what's on the agenda for you recently or for Christmas and how are you doing this year?
We, you know, we don't really do a whole whole lot during the holidays because it's L.A.
So
Yeah, just like yeah people have different traditions. I don't know and also different countries have different traditions
I was just saying my wife is already like she just like saw her her grandmother, but like for the last time
No, that's sorry. Yeah, she she flew home to China and came back and stuff
So so it's kind of and we were looking at trap it like like it's just cost so much
You know for all the tickets and stuff. So
For this time of year, you know, so
Yeah, and um
This year we're just gonna kind of hang out. I mean my son's birthday is is right around Christmas. So, you know
We're gonna we're gonna have my son's first birthday party
My wife wanted us to make him a birthday cake like like to make it for him and
That's fine. So I'm gonna show her how to make a traditional birthday cake in America
Because it's different in China.
I don't know if you ever had an Asian cake before.
I think that she's egg white.
Yeah, well, I have a sister-in-law
who's a Chinese national.
Or, you know, she's from China.
And yeah, so she always brings like the interesting like dish
at parties and stuff like that.
We'll have everyone be like, you know, like bread
and like cheese and stuff like that.
And then, oh.
Ù
Ø¬Ú¾Ù ÙÛÛÚº Ø¨ØªØ§ Ù
ÛØ±Û Ú¯ÙØ³Øª Ù
ÛÙ Ù¾ÛØ§Ø± Ø¨Ø§Ø±ÛØª ÙÛÚ©Ù Ù
ÛÙ Ø§Ù
Ø±ÛÚ©Û Ø³Û ÙØ·ÙÙ
I speak Hindi, but I don't know what he was just playing. I couldn't, couldn't not hear.
I heard the word pyar, pyar means love, but I don't know what the, I couldn't hear, I couldn't hear
That was a treat for you guys, you got to see it.
What kind of song was that?
That was just a Hindu song.
Hindi.
Yeah, I enjoy that kind of music, Hindu music.
I think Hindi, yeah.
Yeah, you speak Hindi.
What's it called?
Hindi.
When I said, I said, when you were off, I said,
I said, I don't know, I don't understand.
Because I couldn't quite hear the words.
I heard the word piata, I think, which means love.
But I couldn't quite make out what they were saying.
So when you're listening to that music,
if you ever hear the word hey, you
might hear the word hey a lot at the end of a sentence.
That just means is.
That means, my name, well, my name, Yeri is.
So, they say is at the end.
Oh, God.
Now, I know where our cameras turn off on.
There we go.
I hear it's all messed up.
Yeah, yeah, hey, how much does this cost?
So you're speaking, that's Hindi?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, wow. So yeah, I mean, I just know I learned a lot of it from just like from like the holy books and the like the mantra and like, you know, just like studying the religion.
But it's like, you know, that's just a very, it's a very small part. Well, it's actually a very big part of their language, but it's like still like it's a very small part of the alphabet.
But it's a beautiful language. And it's like, it really does have these like, it's great tonal effects. And like, it's really
It can be huge bliss, you know, like the mantra, I don't know if you've ever heard of the mantra practice, but it's like
it's
It's one of the best ways to like calm your mind
I think for anybody it's just like a way to focus your mind and like to stop all these thoughts coming at once by focusing on a specific
obscure kind of mantra
But it's like it's been so effective for me. It's basically it's really saved my life in meditation
I don't know Howard Sturm used to say something similar. It's like
Having a meditation technique really is like I had a big impact in my life
and
Luckily, I'm good at sleeping and stuff like that
Uh programming
I want to show you but I want you want to show you this video I made and so you can like kind of this is about the yoginis
There's like 64 of them and um in India, right?
There's like coffee over 64 arts. It's in the comma sutra. I think they list them and there's like one and and uh, so
This is called up silver threads the rise of the ogenis. So each one is associated with a different art, but see if you
See if you liked it. I made this video see if you like it. Let's see. There you go
In the void temple
And the yagan has
Watching what you become
I walk the corridor with a black light breeze
City and floor and the ash like snow
Every door got a name I don't say for free
But it knows my face, it knows my soul
Bare one standing where the fog turns gold
Eyes like moons with a sharp and calm
I came broken, I leave in cold
Threading my chest like a silent song
Silver thread pulled me through
To my fear in a simple truth
If I fall
Let it be four
If I burn
Let it be
64 doors
If you came to haunt me, take a number
This temple's guarded, this art is paid
Mirror oracle, show me the cost
Show me the me, I would've lost
Y'all can hear you whisper through indigo haze
Make it practice, make it day
So I breathe once, slow and clean
Say one honest thing unseen
Not to impress, not to perform
64 doors, I open 64 yards, I hold yoganists in the smoke, they're watching, turn my voice
in the geometry, turn my s-
I kind of just kind of end of the moment, but there you go. Hey, um
Dogs simple this one. I mean I had to get a few of these because my dogs have stepped on them so many times. They broke them
Oh, no
Oh, my gosh, you guys like see see i'm not even kidding. Here's another one
Do you like Doritos Locos tacos?
Yeah, I like anything to read those
as long as they don't have like lime flavor.
Joni, what did you ask for?
You said chow wagons.
Oh, you said, I don't see a request.
So you said, I don't see a request, Joni.
You have a request?
Hey, I'm like, just thinking of this, Beth.
Have you heard of a movie called Flamin' Hot?
Mm, tell me.
There's a movie called Flamin' Hot and what it's about is the guy that came up with the
idea for Flamin' Hotch.
I think we're out of movie ideas, guys.
I like the Flamin' Hotch, he goes.
I know, but I mean, is it 90, is it 150 pages?
I just built cheese all over myself, I'm sorry.
Although like Elon Musk was talking and he was like, you know,
there's a lot of movies about inventions, but there's really very few if any movies
about bringing products to market. It's one thing to invent something,
it's another to bring it to market.
Actually, I can I can play I can play that one second. Oh, you have a special request for a song
Hold on a second
Okay
They can be the person that bought me dinner that from a Taco Bell, that's so nice of you and
Absolutely you have a song
I'm gonna look terrible. I'm like 15 years older than I normally don't.
Tuffy and, ugh.
Okay.
Ready?
um disney signed a thing with i i think it was saura yeah saura whereas saura gets to use
some disney's ip so people can make their own short form disney movies which by the way might sound
The it's great, but Disney owns any movie that you make with Sora like that
So if you make something, it's really good. Disney gets to put it on Disney plus
Under like cuz they're gonna have some sort of thing that like it's like full of AI shorts, but nobody make it paid for it
So you can make a short it'll be on Disney plus you don't get paid
Isn't that really generous of Disney to let people use their cartoons?
That's real generous.
Whatcha doin?
i never saw that what oh
shoni that wasn't the right song that wasn't the right song
i'm oh uh hopefully i'm gonna use uh i guess the music finally needs some music figured out
for the the show i'm working on um
I'm gonna use a band called McFly that for some reason Americans don't know. I don't get it
They're like really big
Around the world. Uh-huh. Is it like after Marty McFly back to the future? Yeah, actually, you know, it's funny is um
Christopher Lloyd will sometimes do the intros for uh
Um one of those good the song called the year 3000 where it's like he's talking to Einstein. Where are we?
oh oh we're in the year the year 3000 and then like the songs are playing are
like you know for he did this thing for their their their their 21st birthday
party and well also they do it for him I don't know but
Yeah, it's all it's all to they get the name from from back to the future, of course. Oh my wife actually introduced him to my wife
Years ago back when they were teenagers, right? This is how long my wife and I have been together
They're now pushing 40
And she hadn't seen them and so I had them playing from one of the recent concerts and I said hey
You remember that band and I told her and she's like, oh, yeah
Yeah, I was like and I just pointed to the screen and she's like and she freaked because they don't they don't really look anything the same like
way different now
So
That's good
And I don't know if you remember Jesse camp. You remember him Jesse camp from I want to be a VJ on MTV
He was the crazy guy who won
Yeah, Jesse he had like the long hair
Yeah, man. He was always stuck like this and like maybe like I've known him since 2005
I met him backstage at a concert and
Like what was funny is I actually bought his album because he came on the radio show that I was working on like you know
At like back when the album came out. I didn't talk to him and then
But I I didn't know that that he and MTV had this big problem and whatever
so
Um, I told him, hey dude, I bought your album and I see you around, it's great.
Like, why didn't you guys ever make a follow-up?
And he flipped.
He goes, what?
You bought it?
Like, yeah, we sold 300,000 copies.
Oh.
And ever since then, I've been pretty cool, so I want him to do a couple songs for the show just because I like him a lot.
And Dave too, the guy who was second place, Dave, he and I have worked out together.
He works out over at Universal LA Fitness, so I've known him for 15 years.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, I'm Jesse Longer, but yeah, it's it's it's strange that I know both of them
but
LA's a
People think Hollywood's like this big town and I'm like, no man
There's like there's like three gyms in LA or four or maybe if you go to them
You'll see like pretty much every celebrity that doesn't have a gym in their house
You like that's and even some that do they just want to get out
I think Alexandra's I think she's ripping me a new one maybe but I'm not sure
But uh
Yeah, I'm not seeing something dark side of brushes internet. Oh, um, wow
Well ghost didn't come up. I don't know. I don't know what's going on tonight, but I think I'll have to
You have a home gym. I think you know, it's like I guess beat is too popular. And so, you know, no one comes to my show anymore
Yeah, I don't like going to the gym anymore. I call it a pre-club
Now I had a company build an actual gym in my house like with real
gym machines that you'd see like like
This is right. That's a life fitness machine right there. That's a but I sit right behind me
But no like downstairs. I've got cybex weight machines and all that cable crossovers
You know
Smith machine
That kind of thing pull down
Sorry
If anyone else wants to come up or I might have to end it soon
Um, yeah, I think I think there's a slight emergency, so I need to, uh, maybe get off
right now, but, um, my wife wants to watch Landman and, uh, and do weed and I'm kind
of in pain.
I don't know.
It's hard for me to speak.
Uh, I've had this with jaw surgery, so yeah, uh, I figured I'd better get it done now before
Yeah, I mean I was in an accident and you know, I need to have
Actually have bone grafting and stuff. It's it's hmm. I've been putting it off
Because it hurts
Just see the community see the community board
Yeah, I'm spazzling over here
Who spasms me?
Oh, I just like my muscles are spasmed.
Yeah.
Okay, well, um, do you know beta?
Huh?
Do you know beta?
Beta?
Yeah.
I mean, I'm...
I met quite a few people on your show,
but I don't, the name doesn't ring a bell.
Sorry, I've met you. Apologies.
If I end, you can go to Vita's Kitties,
and she has a panel, and she always has,
she lets everybody up on it, so.
Oh, okay.
She's really...
I mean, I said, my wife wants to watch Landman
and kind of get ready, because it's, you know,
it's getting towards her, but it's midnight,
past midnight here, so.
And like, you know, I try to sleep 12 hours a day,
so I get little naps, you know?
Yeah, I've been taking naps all day, for sure,
because I'm sick, I've been sick for like a week,
and then I had this like orange pill,
I think it was like a Norco or something,
I'm not sure what it was, like an orange pill,
but,
It got me really relaxed though.
I didn't like maybe sleep because I thought
I was asleep all day, but I didn't know.
Well, there's energy from it.
Like, if I take Ambien, I get energy.
It's like so weird.
I can't like, I don't like fall asleep to it and stuff.
I'm like.
I give my Ambien to my wife.
Um, anyway, but yeah, yeah.
Dude, morphine makes me hyper.
The only thing I've found that actually doesn't make me hyper and I think it's a miracle drug
It is a dilotted because I could be feeling sick as can be like shaking like like sweats
horrible fever and
You know as soon as they give me an IV of a few milligrams of dilotted man like
I am good, or it's in tablet form, but that's just you can get tablets down, you know, sometimes, you know, I can't even drink water, that's how sick I'm talking about, and they gave me an IV if I lauded, and all of a sudden, I'm fine, you know?
I feel like nothing ever happened.
So, uh, uh-huh.
Hold on a second.
I don't understand why that's not over the counter, man.
I don't understand this treating us
like we're like children's shit.
It's really fucking stupid.
That's why like my surgeries hurt more
because doctors are afraid of being prosecuted
for forgiving pain medication.
That is-
Well, after Michael Jackson, right?
Yeah, but I mean like at the point where you have people who are awake during surgery, you know
Like like the guy where Michael Jackson that was propofol and
Depending on how much from fall works on me in it or it doesn't but
The problem, you know, I don't know if you remember the guy who is monitoring him walked away now when you have somebody on popa fall
Your that their life is literally in your hands
if they
If their breathing starts to suppress you need to immediately hop on that shit
Oh, but I studied
I was I was I say pre-med anyway, so I'm I love this shit
So
Nobody actually dies from a heroin overdose
What they die from is
For getting that the brain telling
For forgetting to tell the lungs to breathe, you know, so you could pump someone up
with tons of heroin or whatever and they could be on a respiratory
And if it was breathing for them
They would live, you know
They might vomit
But they'll live
And it's just interesting, like how we bastardize drugs.
You know, just recently, like they classified Fentanyl
as a, I never, well, yeah, I've had Fentanyl
when I was having surgery once,
but they cut as a weapon of mass destruction, right?
Well, when my wife had her, gave birth to our son,
Um, I spoke to the anesthesiologist and he told me that he was giving her, um, small doses of fentanyl very frequently to, you know,
You guys can continue. It's me. Thank you.
Yeah. Um, he said it's better to give small doses frequently than large doses infrequently.
Um, and anyway, it worked great and I mean it helped her out a lot
The surgery I mean she was in the hospital for a week. So
But it helped her and and it was a I don't see like what's bad, it's not even a new medication
You know ghosts say I think say hi to Patrick or say hi to I'm sorry captain have fun
We went to talk like one time before I don't know though
Either way, it's nice. Yeah, I think so too. I think we're at least one time
If not, it's nice to meet you man. Yeah, I saved you sir. How you doing?
Cuz I think I called you blackbill if I remember correctly
Like looks maxing I think that's what I call but it's not a big deal. I was talking around but how are you doing tonight, man?
I'm tired. I just like woke up a while ago. Yeah. I feel that. Yeah, I hurt my leg. I'm doing better. I fucked my leg up like last week, man. It's been, I'm finally doing a little bit better. Uh, I don't know what I did to it, to be honest with you.
Hypercinder or whatever. Yeah, and I didn't like that first date her and the second date hurt worse and the third day
I couldn't even walk so like it built up so I don't actually know what I did to it
But now it's getting better though. I didn't go to the doctor
Yeah
But it's getting better now. I'm not feeling hopeful. So now I don't I don't know what happened
Okay, maybe you got lucky the the same thing happened to my dad back in like 89 or 90
He was in pursuit of a guy
and this dude
Pulled him off a bridge and on onto the street below
And it turned my dad's knee like
So and that affected him until he could get a new knee like after 9-eleven
So I'll tell you what dude
Let me argue against myself because I always argue with other people
But let me use logic against myself
After that third day when I literally couldn't get out of bed
I should have went to the hospital and that that was the most logical sense ever and I didn't follow it at all
Luckily, I'm getting better now, but I don't know a miracle. I mean it took me a week
But even after that third day though the rest of those like five other days
I should have went like I was in it like I couldn't even like move and shit like I barely moved. I should have went
There's no use like if there's no logical excuse why I shouldn't have went I
Was just being stubborn. I guess like fuck it. I've always got over everything else, but I'm not a young man anymore
Well, I mean going to the hospital really fucking sucks. It's cold. It's annoying. It's slow
Boring. Yeah, you have to move your fucking leg what you can't
Yeah, and like if you're in pain like I mean
I'll take like a backpack with me with like a charger and like a whole bunch of stuff in there and like
Because like basically like get kind of like a camping
concentrate, I know I'm gonna be sitting there for hours.
So I sit that battery back and watching stuff on my computer
for hours, you know?
Are you talking about once you get like checked in
because luckily I have family and we're close to like,
and we're like close as in like, like, you know,
family wise also we're close proximity.
So I can call them back, hey, bring me a charger.
Hey, bring me.
Which is awesome, which I really appreciate you know families like the number one thing and life brother
Yeah, I don't have that out here, but what what I'm getting at is that I know I'm gonna be
Camping or something like you're gonna bring everything in one back like
Serious like you sit in the emergency room sometimes I don't know if you're from a big city, but if you
I'm not from a big city, but even not from being from a big city if that's not serious
They check other people in in front of you even though they came later and like you can sit there for hours, man
Yeah
You know I'm in Hollywood
Hollywood what California is but Hollywood's not but yeah, I know what you mean. Yeah, the
Well, I I'm from West Virginia, sir. So it's a lot bigger than it is around here
Yeah, yeah, well the one thing we have is like okay. Well
So Hollywood is more like a high school or like a small small town like everybody knows everybody like
and like rumors spread that are not,
I mean, I'm not about being anybody,
I'm just, but I was a fitness model and like,
I got up one morning and there was like an industry,
like this letter that goes out and stuff
and that this one, and it had been in the media
that I assigned a contract with a model,
with a company I knew he had a meeting with, you know?
So like rumors spread just like high school out here, man, and it is so everybody knows
around here.
Here's the difference though around here when rumors spread, you know what we do around
here?
We fucking, if you're a man, you fucking fight about it, like, well, you know, what's
happened?
That that happened over at the Hollywood play, and I got a question, you were, you were,
you said you were, what do you just say you were?
You were a fit.
What do you just say?
Did you do that so or do you have something like managing you no, I had an agent which is why like I found out he called me
He's like hey, is this true world? What what do you do and do it? Signing deals behind my back?
Here's my second question though. You you said it was like fitness mind. I'm sure your shirt was off and shit
Is that kind of like only fans brother? I
With my shirt off. I mean, I was usually selling like getting paid for your body and your sexual image
I'm pretty sure that's kind of I mean
I'm not gonna say building. I mean at the same time I was I was I mean like I
Was 50 pounds bigger than I am now. It was more like bodybuilding. Yeah, I mean, well, yeah, obviously
I was uh, I mean I'm six foot four and there's very few tall muscular guys who have like like lean
You know, I most guys who are like big and muscular. I'd like you know the big bone like Eddie Hall kind of thing
The strongest man in the world, you know what he looks like he looks like an old-ass Viking with a big
Asthomic, but he's fucking he can lift like dude
He can live so much that's like a I'm sure they're on shit, but that's like a natural like it's not like a little like
It's not like toned. It's not like Arnold Schwarzenegger back in the day. That's shit
The way you're getting guys to do you're missing things, okay, what they do
That kind of guy that can lift the most that's what I'm talking about. That's what those power lifters do they throw weight they throw it
I don't do any of that shit.
Are you talking about toning your shit?
I go one, two, three, four, five, six.
Hold it on the muscle for four to six seconds and then back down.
And I have to admit, if I'm not gay or nothing,
but I have to admit that you would be more sexually attracted to a female
than somebody like Eddie would be,
but Eddie would fucking destroy you.
He would literally lift you like he'd fucking throw you.
Well, I mean, I would weight you 20 right now.
I mean, yeah, exactly what his he set the world record.
He'd fucking throw you.
Yeah.
But I mean, like once again, you're using throw.
That's why I called you look at how much that guy can actually
lift.
I mean, I'm not saying you couldn't lift, but lift.
All right, just go ahead and YouTube it.
You can see how much you can actually, you know, YouTube it.
YouTube it you can the strongest man in the world YouTube it you can see how much he can actually live does YouTube it
Yeah, yeah, I want to see them lift like like actually the way like Mike Mincer and like this like scientists have said like the best way
To actually exhaust the muscle
because that's why like I mean I'll gain 20 pounds of muscle in a month is because I
Just I work out for an hour a week and then the rest of the week
I just eat lots of really good food and I get lots of really good sleep or as much as I can and
Then I grow because that you grow in your rest period. You don't you don't grow when you're training
But I don't want to talk too much into it because obviously I don't know what I'm talking about
I just know those dudes are a lot stronger like they those dudes that have like the belly on them
But they're like that it's like the offensive linemen and fucking the NFL like they're a lot stronger
You look at Dorian Yates and he could beat those guys in his day he could beat those guys and go out and compete
But he was a fighter though. He wasn't a lifter, but that was a big-ass dude that took he definitely took some
I mean not powerlifting but body lifting like they all take that shit like yeah
I mean what I do and also you got I went from being a football player to being a hiker
I lived in the wilderness for a year without electricity doing survival school training and all this
So like I did all that kind of shit. So like yeah, you really can't like, you know be bodybuilding when you're doing that
You're you do look better
I mean, I'm not trying to I'm not being gay here
You do look better than them, but those dudes like those they look like they're Vikings
I got the belly on but they're biggest fuck and like
You can even say like they're kind of fat like dude those dudes are like real like those are the ones that can fucking
Pick up a fucking car
Are you familiar with the guy adorian Yates cuz cuz he's like he's
280 at five foot
Eight I think or five foot nine some five foot nine. Maybe I don't know but anyway
He worked out the way that I'm talking about but he was he had you know a lot of steroids and stuff
He was able to work out three hours a week
But yeah, that doesn't matter though like because have you like like Wes Watson are you filming with him?
I mean, recently this dude's loss like what like 30 pounds now like his arms look skinny. That's because he can't afford his fucking stairwork schedule anymore.
Dorian Dorian's a multimillionaire. Anyway, he was Mr. Olympia six times all that. So, but but he did it when he was Mr. Olympia, he only worked out like I'm at the max hours a week.
And he did it like I say, um, without momentum that momentum is an outside aiding force. That's why I like when I see those guys
lifting
You know
Yeah, but I'm talking about I
Okay, let me go ahead and grant. Let me give you some middle ground here. Let us agree. I grant that I
Agree with that if you're taking that shit and you only do that
Genetics all I agree with all that but somebody like as the same Eddie how the strong if he was the strongest man
I don't know if he still is but him, you know
I know I talked to him two weeks ago. Yeah. Yeah, okay. Yeah him somebody like him though
Like it's not about all that shit like that dude's literally he literally has the world record like
Yeah
Yeah, that's uh, I'm not saying it's all natural obviously, but he's definitely not like people like you that are like toned down
Like the fat to what is it called fat to skin ratio?
What is it called like you want to be like skin tight and shit? He's not like that and that
I mean
He's very limited in what about either he's like seven foot something and he's an endo mesomorph
Argument like with the rock because the rock is big as fuck and obviously eats a lot of calories
But he can do that as well because you know, he's not natural. That's another well
He's another endo mesomorph. He's a he's a Samoan
There's three body types like ecto Mesto and endo Mesto
And like, Ecto is like, I'm very long, I mean, like, you know, I mean, my arms like alone are just, you know, very, very long.
And my bones are not like, you know, super wide, like, you know, like, one of my cousins and I, like, he actually has less muscle mass than me, but he looks bigger because he, and he gains mass easier because he's just got big bones and his metabolism is a little slower.
I have a fast metabolism and like my I've got thin long bones. Does that make sense?
Yeah, it makes sense
I think one of my favorite things and I can't relate because I obviously don't like I'm not a body butter
But back in high school when I used to live, you know what the best thing was when you drink a lot of water
Where you're working out and you get in you pump dude. I used to take pictures. I looked I looked twice as big
Mm-hmm. Yeah, I mean not twice as big I'm exaggerating obviously, but I did look bigger. I'm like
Well, that's I drank like I'm like fucking drink a lot of water and then I became bloated or something
I'm talking about my arms though. I never had
Well, your muscles are made of mostly water and and like a lot of people will disagree with like when I'm about to save it like a
Diet of 60% carbohydrates
is actually the most beneficial for and then the rest I mean, I think that only 50% fats in the rest protein
I'll tell you what like 80% of people will say like they don't understand this is like if you want to lose weight
All you have to do you probably don't even have to work out necessarily. I mean you do but
You just got to like take you got to like take in less car like you can't eat my car
Yeah, it's calorie. It's a calorie thing and that's America's biggest problem
Yeah, I mean, like Mike Minster, he was saying, he's like, he goes, you know, because he was saying, well, you know, what if, you know, there was certain foods make you fat, what don't, I mean, I mean, there are certain foods, yeah, they have a higher glycemic index, they digest slower, whatever.
Isn't that kind of like, oh, yeah, go ahead, I didn't mean to interrupt, sorry.
three thousand calories per day
but you're only in taking two
thousand calories a day.
It doesn't matter if those
calories are in it.
Simply mayonnaise and table
sticker, you're still going to
lose weight.
Exactly.
But when you when you talk about like body butters and shit like they have to eat that because they they're woken up
And a lot of people like to get fat before that but a lot of people have to maintain that shit
It's like the flash, you know the flash from DC universe. He runs so fast
He has things like he has to eat like 33,000 calories a day or whatever because he runs like you break the fuck. Yeah
Yeah, that's like scientific, but yeah, I get what you're saying. I'm not trying to debate it man
Well, I mean, and something is a quick thing about the flash, you know, I've got a studio full of like action figures from Florida ceiling and one quick thing about the flash.
If he's not invulnerable like Superman, how does his hair and his eyeballs and like his skin stay on his body?
I mean the man would just run so fast. That is a good question
I thought you were gonna go with like how would he dodge a bullet and I was gonna say like it's like Neo
He doesn't have to dodge it. He can vibrate at it at a certain speed. He passed right through him
But how does I can answer your question actually because actually I can answer your question you want to know why?
They make the the makers
Love him. They literally thought about this and they call it the speed force. That's why
Yeah
Like enter the speed force though, I mean
Speed force brother well, that's recent but anyway
Well, listen, you answered I I had the same argument and then I heard the speed force and then he forces something that we can't we don't know
They made they made it the fuck up. So we don't know
But we can blame it on speed force
It's like why can you do some things one time and the other things other time like they blamed it on speed force
But you do make a good point also
Vibrating at the same speed as a wall and you're gonna run through it. That doesn't make any sense either
You can't vibrate the same frequency as a wall
Well fuck I don't care if you're going like I mean unless you're going like fucking like a godspeed unless you're going like
Do you I even let's say you go like fucking 2000 miles per hour?
You're not gonna run through that wall. You're gonna destruct that wall, but you know what that wall is gonna do to you
It's gonna destruct you as well, sir. You're gonna be fucked up
Yeah, I mean it's not I mean I I'm a pilot and it's not just about speed that would be about about the actual like
No, you're talking about quantum physics. We're in this like we have to get exactly
Vibrations of the frequency
Yeah, of that vibration that would they would they would equal at it. No, I'll tell you well
We're humans. There's nothing on the humanly possible that we can vibrate and the first comes enough
to go through a fucking solid object there.
We can't do that.
Like us, personally, we can't do that.
I like the concept of it, but that's
why there's such thing as.
That's a speed force. That's what they call it. Yeah, we can fire things at ninety nine point nine
It's not gonna go through it, but it's not gonna phase through it
There's a difference go through or phase through you're not gonna phase through it. You can't phase through it
I don't give a fuck how quick you can do it unless you get to that point
You know unless you get to that one point where we can actually fire that just quick enough
Then we'll go through it
Yeah
Actually, I take my point back section. Oh, you know, that's I'm just hype up. I don't even actually know if that would work
I mean theoretically it would
Well, like I know like like like one of the airplanes my company used to have it doesn't exist anymore
But like my partner put an afterburner on it now now it the airframe was made for this thing to you know
Go 350 miles an hour. It's an L 39 albatross fighter jet. Okay, and and if you want to look at the one
I'm talking about it was called the wild child. It was the fastest one in the world
Because my partner put an afterburner on it. So it would cruise at 545
So anyway, but it has straight wings. Okay, mind you
So you go into a dive you go and like, you know, you start you
Can really lose control. I was afraid that he was gonna rip the wings off that sucker
Um, I mean at a certain speed air becomes like solid, you know
so
Hold on I'm looking I don't know the p.m. I
Don't know. I don't really keep up with a lot of stuff going on right now
is
Oh, oh, you're talking about oh god, that's gross freaking. No
I'm talking like pump and pose. God. That's like
Okay, that's like oil and like filler and Viagra and
It makes your muscles swell up and no, I don't think that's a very good thing to use
I know a lot of people do use that to try to like enhance certain areas like like if you have certain areas that like
Like
Better okay, so like maybe you want to make this muscle look a little bigger
You might want to inject that or maybe you have like a problem trying to make this peak
Look like like a little bit different
So you want to inject it to get a little bit more of a peak look at it
You know that kind of a thing so
You know as opposed to a consistent this muscle side as it's just the way it connects so
You know
You can see where that connects differently
So these guys will take this stuff and inject it and it'll give it more of a ball look and equal it out
Flexwheeler was really famous for doing that kind of stuff problem is a lot of that
Unless it's by like up John
But other than an actual pharmaceutical company some of that stuff is they found
Plastics in it and that plastic doesn't leave your muscle. It'll stay in there and
That's bad
We'll see. My receiver is not, that's why it's dark here. Hold on.
There we go
All right
Oh motherfucker, what is that? So what's is that? It gives a hint in the input button. No go back
There we are, okay
It's hard to get my my camera up without hitting the receiver too. That's the thing
Like old
Well, I'm the only one here. I guess I'm gonna get out of here. Nice chat with you guys.
Oh, um, that's interesting.
Louvering go fire or
I'm a guy who's retired, living in Hollywood, used to do stunts, used to acquire music rights, did a whole bunch of different jobs in Hollywood.
Now I'm just a dad.
No, I'm a married man, dude. I've got a baby boy I can give back to.
Well, thank you very much for saying what she'll do to you.
If you're on Twitter, hit me up.
Always nice to meet friends of psych.
Yeah, my wife's seen psych before.
Yeah, she's been here when I talked to him.
She's right downstairs.
She can hear me talk to him now, or if he was here.
If it's the whole gay thing, I mean, we live in Hollywood, like, I mean, I, you know, of course, I know people that are gay.
I can't, like, have a problem with that because, you know, I mean, I live in Hollywood and working.
A lot of my bosses work, you know.
Oh, my God, shut up, dude. I'm in California.
Ha ha ha ha!
$90 for what I bought 60
Mmm
Versaig not to offend
Oh, son of a bitch
That's five
Oh
Oh, they don't have
Oh, shit.